Seller Central UI based fulfillment.
To assign an order to a delivery associate, first select "Manage Orders" from the Orders menu.
Find the order you would like to complete and select "Confirm" under the "Appointment" column.
Here you can add any delivery notes and schedule the delivery.
For a doorstep delivery, select a specific date from the range and confirm.
For an attended delivery, you can first call the customer to align schedules.
Select the agreed-upon date and time, and then confirm.
For a room of choice delivery, choose from the options the customer has provided and confirm.
Once the delivery date has been set, select Assign to choose the delivery associate that will complete
the job.
Choose your delivery associate from the list.
Once you select "Save", all the relevant details are shown on the Manage Orders page.
Once the order is delivered, you can select the "Complete Job" button.
Use Seller Central UI based fulfillment to enter the order completion details.
Enter the delivery associate, the date, and the completion time.
Select "Confirm".
The order will now be shown as completed on the Manage Orders page.